[Subtitles by danielsangeo]
[fzzt]
--AAAAGH!
Oh! That was horrible!
Wait... no!
What is this?!
THIS ISN'T MASSACHUSETTS!
Oh no...
Oh, God! They fucked me!
I TOLD THEM EXACTLY WHAT TO DO
AND THEY FUCKED ME!
[screaming]
THIS IS WORSE THAN EVERYTHING!
Oh, God! I feel strange...!
Dizzy...!
Is this gravity...?!
Oh! Okay...!
[whimpering]
[hyperventilating]
Okay... well, I gotta do something...
This day's going to shit.
All right. There's something over there.
I'm going for it.
NnyaaaaaaaAAAAAAA--
Oof!
Are you kidding me?
Fuck.
Oh, he's hiding.
Gee, where could he have gone?
Oh, I think I see him.
I think I see him.
Yeah, that's right.
Shoot away the madness.
Oh, lovely. Here's a
wonderful fucking omen.
I would get a picture
of this tattooed on me.
This so concisely sums up everything.
Just everything.
And he had a helmet on so what
does that say about me?
Well, I'm not taking it.
It has germs now.
Oh, God! What's happening?!
Gotta keep moving.
Ha!
[vortigaunt charging up]
WAAAAAAAH!
NO!
[houndeye charging up]
STOP!
WHERE ARE YOU?!
[houndeye attack]
BLAH!
YOU HAVE ALL OF
INFINITE SPACE TO TELEPORT TO!
I'VE ALREADY CLAIMED THIS...
horrible... chunk...
Okay, I guess I'll make my way
to the big thing, then...
...blow my brains out, I don't know...
Ha!
...don't miss, don't miss!
Oh, good, it didn't flip.
I'm not sure how these are floating;
I guess they're filled with a lighter gas?
I mean, if it was magnetism, wouldn't
that affect some of my suit or weapons?
Actually, I don't know
what metals are on me.
Dah!
Eee!
NYAAH!
Okay, don't freak out...
Don't freak out...!
I SAID DON'T FREAK OUT, DAMMIT!
OKAY!
NAH!
NUH!
I'M TOTALLY NOT FREAKING OUT RIGHT NOW!
BECAUSE... THIS IS ME NOT FREAKING OUT!
WHAT DO I HAVE TO
FREAK OUT OVER, ANYWAY?!
NOTHING! BECAUSE I'M NOT!
I'M JUST NAVIGATING FLOATING
OBSTACLE COURSE THAT LOOKS LIKE A...
GIANT... PLATE-BALANCING TRICK
DESIGNED BY H. R. GIGER!
FUCK YOU, REALITY!
YOU'RE FULL OF SHIT!
AND... BONE PILLAR THINGS AND...
BREATHABLE ATMOSPHERE...!
NYAH!
...wwwwAAAAAAH!
REALITY'S BROKE!
Why is there gravity?!
I look below this thing and
there's just the void!
Wah!
Waa-aaa-AAAH!
Okay, I'm clear for
landing on the hell blob.
So, am I supposed to believe this thing is
dense enough to cause gravitational pull?
I don't fucking think so!
Not only is that stupid but that would've
yanked me sideways with that top platform.
A ledge. Why not?
Whoa-ho-ho!
[houndeye charging up, Xen crystal bolt]
WAH!
[houndeye charging up]
WHAT'S HAPPENING?!
[houndeye attack, Xen crystal bolt]
WAH!
Shoot the madness... shoot the madness...
No!
[Xen crystal bolt]
WAAH!
[Xen crystal bolts]
LET ME IN!
God, Je..!
[Xen crystal bolts]
[straining]
Ah, a first aid kit. I guess
somebody else made it this far.
I wonder how many explorers they
just dumped out here.
Probably a lot.
Maybe that's why I couldn't
get a helmet: they ran out.
What the hell is this thing?
[Xen crystal bolts]
Ah! Fuck!
PURPLE... PROACTIVE... BUG ZAPPERS!
[Xen crystal bolt]
AH!
FUCK OFF!
[houndeye charging up]
NO!
SHUT UP!
[houndeye charging up]
STOP! NO!
FOR CRYING OUT L-- THERE!
Yeah, go do your little dance...
you freak.
Yeah, you can't even do THAT right.
[Xen crystal bolt]
AH!
Oh!  I-- you're not worth it.
Not yet.
What IS this thing?
Wah! What happened?
Did it steal a piece of my soul?
Give it back!
No... it's not really worth it.
Well, I guess I have a water
source... maybe.
Stop that!
Well, I guess I'll check out the interior.
Maybe I can find a weak point and blow
this up. That would make me feel better.
Fucking nightmare.
Oh, there IS something in here.
Well... yeah, it's about
what I was expecting.
A lot of water.
If anything here is edible,
I can go for weeks.
Well, guess this is my new home!
I'll get settled in.
Is this a mushroom? I'm no
stranger to mushrooms.
Oh, it lights up.
Dream décor for a stoner.
It does make the place cozier.
What the hell is this?
Eh, I'll try and eat it later.
Really, I need to eat those
things I killed on the ledge first
because they're going
to rot if I wait too long.
I'm REALLY hoping I can find a
way to cook them
because dinner is going to be
harsh enough as it is.
Yeah, turn on all the mushrooms,
I don't care about the power bill.
Okay, those blinking lights are
annoying; I'll take care of that later.
This, actually, isn't THE worst apartment
I've ever had. It's close, though.
What's this? A bird cage?
Well, I'm pretty sure I can't
eat rhombuses, so you're free to go.
Enjoy.
Well, they'd better figure out
how to fly out of here
or else I'm gonna swat 'em later.
No, I don't want to waste the ammo.
I haven't done a full perimeter check yet.
So, where am I going to sleep?
Oh no!
Well, I can't call this an earthquake.
Oh God! Ah!
OKAY, THIS APARTMENT'S DEFINITELY
THE SECOND WORST I'VE HAD!
IT'S STILL NOT INFECTED WITH BEDBUGS!
WHAT IS THIS?! IS THIS A TELEPORTER?!
IT COULD SEND ME INTO SPACE!
I COULD DECOMPRESS!
OH GOD! THE ROOM'S CLOSING IN ON ME!
THESE ARE TEETH! IT'S ALIVE!
THE ROOM'S GOING TO EAT ME!
SHIT!
OKAY, NOT A LOT OF FUCKING OPTIONS!
[fzzt]
AAAAH!
[exhales]
Great.
[distant thumping]
Hey, what's that noise?
[distant growling]
[distant thumping]